[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我认为这是一个很好的机会
&gt;&gt; Kyle: I thought it was a good opportunity for
让我们快速回顾一下我们在这个研讨会上所经历的一切。
us to take a quick look back at what we've gone through over this workshop.
正如我所说的，这代表了一种基线，我真的想要所有的JavaScript
As I said, this represents kind of the baseline that I really want all JavaScript
开发人员感觉他们可以到达。
developers to feel like they can get to.
所以这是一种全场压力，让我们发布消息，
So it's kind of a full court press saying, let's get the word out,
让我们让人们练习并试图达到这一点。
let's get people practicing and trying to get to that point.
所以，让我们确保我们明白我们的来龙去脉，
So, let's make sure we understand where we've come,
因为从研讨会开始到目前为止，我们已经走过了很长一段路。
cuz we've come quite a way since the beginning of the workshop, so far.
所以，首先，用你自己的话，你会如何向我描述什么是回调地狱？
So first, in your own words, how would you describe to me what callback hell is?
到底是什么？
What is it really?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：控制反转。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Inversion of control.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：控制反转是关键方面之一。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Inversion of control is one of the key aspects.
还有什么？
What else?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：顺序错误。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Out of sequence.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：非局部、非顺序推理。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: The non-local, non-sequential reasoning.
那么什么是回拨地狱呢？
So what is callback hell?
回调地狱不仅仅是回调模式的不足，
Callback hell isn't deficiency of the callbacks pattern alone,
当你除了回电什么都没有的时候。
when you don't have anything else but the callback.
它无法解决这些主要缺陷。
It's not capable of addressing these major deficiencies.
其中一个是控制的版本。
One of them being a version of control.
其中之一是非局部非顺序推理。
One of them being non-local non-sequential reasoning.
所以回拨
So callbacks,
虽然它们是原子的基本构件，但我们所依据的一切
while they're the atomic fundamental building block upon which everything we
正在做，即使是那些花哨的生成器的东西仍然有回叫发生。
doing, even that fancy generator stuff is still got callbacks happening.
但如果顶部没有这些额外的图案，
But without those additional patterns on top,
回调不能解决这些问题。
the callbacks are not capable of addressing these issues.
因此，我们需要将更高阶的模式放在它们之上，以解决这些问题。
So we need to put higher order patterns on top of them to address those problems.
这就是回拨地狱的真面目吗？
That's what callback hell really is?
你知道，这与嵌套和压痕真的没有什么关系。
You know is that really has very little to do with the nesting an indentation.
这是巨大的副作用，好吧。
That's a side symptom of vast, okay.
什么是承诺？
What is a Promise?
我给了两个或
I gave two or
三种不同的隐喻方式或思考许诺的方式。
three different metaphoric ways or ways of thinking about what a Promise is.
从概念上讲，什么是承诺？
A conceptually speaking, what is a Promise?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：它是一个值的占位符。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's a placeholder for a value.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：值的占位符。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Placeholder for a value.
这是未来的芝士汉堡对吧？
It's a future cheeseburger, right?
这是一个未来的价值，它是我将在某个时候得到的芝士汉堡。
It's a future value, it's the cheeseburger I'm going to get at some point.
还有什么？
What else is it?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：信任。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Trust.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：这就是它的作用和
&gt;&gt; Kyle: That's what it does and
稍后我们将更多地讨论它的作用。
we'll get to talking more about what it does in just a minute.
但打个比方
But metaphorically,
我至少给了你另外两种方式来思考它的作用。
I gave you at least two other ways of thinking about what it does.
记住，我说过这是一个完成事件。
Remember, I talked about it being a completion event.
就像我们回来的事件监听器
It's like an event listener that we get back and
我们可以注册完成事件，在本例中称为Then事件。
we can register for a completion event, in this case is called the then event.
这是另一种方式，第三种思考方式是，
It's another way and another third way of thinking about it is that,
这是一个回拨管理器。
it's a callback manager.
我们将我们的回调传递给承诺系统
We pass our callback to the promise system and
正如你刚才所说，它以一种给予我们信任的方式来管理它们。
it manages them in a way that gives us that trust as you just said.
我们想要回你的信任。
We want that trust back.
通过将它们传递到承诺系统中，
And by passing them into the promise system,
我们知道承诺系统就是在这种信任的基础上设计的。
we know that promise system are designed with that trust.
因此它解决了一个版本的控件，因为不是将我们的回调传递给
So it solves a version of control because instead of passing our callbacks into
我们不信任的第三方，相反，他们给了我们一个承诺
a third party that we don't trust, instead they give us a promise back
一个值得信赖的系统，我们让那个系统经理打电话给我们。
a trustable system and we let that system manager called us.
所以反转控制反转或
So an invert that inversion of control or
而只是简单地限制我们一直拥有的控制。
rather just simply restraints the control that we always have.
如何暂停发电机？
How do you pause a generator?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：让步。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yield.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：产量，以及如何恢复发电机？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yield, and how do you resume a generator?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：Iterate.Next。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Iterate.next.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：.下一步，组合生成器和
&gt;&gt; Kyle: .next, and what was that one magical trick for combining generators and
一起承诺？
promises together?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：做出承诺。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yield a promise.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：准确地说，产生了一个承诺。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yielding a promise, exactly.
给出一个承诺，然后这个承诺恢复发电机。
Yield a promise and then the promise resumes the generator.
这是准确的，好吗？
It's accurate, okay?
好极了。
Great.
你想了解更多关于发电机的信息。
You want to read more about generators.
除了书之外，我还有一个四部分的博客文章系列来阅读它。
I have a four part blog post series to read about it in addition to the books.
所以有很多东西可以去
So there's plenty to go and
在那里阅读，我挑战你鼓励你去挖掘这一点。
read in there and I challenge you encourage you to go dig in on this.